[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "This, a 12-year-old boy who just calmly takes a shotgun to school and opens fire on classmates in the gym, do we have any idea yet about motive?", "question_tokens": ["This", ",", "a", "12-year-old", "boy", "who", "just", "calmly", "takes", "a", "shotgun", "to", "school", "and", "opens", "fire", "on", "classmates", "in", "the", "gym", ",", "do", "we", "have", "any", "idea", "yet", "about", "motive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "We don't.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "... in the past of America but for 12 years old, it really does take this gun epidemic to a whole new level, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["...", "in", "the", "past", "of", "America", "but", "for", "12", "years", "old", ",", "it", "really", "does", "take", "this", "gun", "epidemic", "to", "a", "whole", "new", "level", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "VB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "Could you tell me exactly what you saw or heard today?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "tell", "me", "exactly", "what", "you", "saw", "or", "heard", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Do you know who the girl was who was 13, who was wounded?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "who", "the", "girl", "was", "who", "was", "13", ",", "who", "was", "wounded", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "WP", "VBD", "CD", ",", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "And are these friends of yours or people that you just know at the school?", "question_tokens": ["And", "are", "these", "friends", "of", "yours", "or", "people", "that", "you", "just", "know", "at", "the", "school", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "They are friends of mine.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "are", "friends", "of", "mine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "But, do you know the boy who used the shotgun?", "question_tokens": ["But", ",", "do", "you", "know", "the", "boy", "who", "used", "the", "shotgun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "sir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "And did you have any indication when you saw him arriving with his bag that he had anything wrong with him, that he was angry or agitated?", "question_tokens": ["And", "did", "you", "have", "any", "indication", "when", "you", "saw", "him", "arriving", "with", "his", "bag", "that", "he", "had", "anything", "wrong", "with", "him", ",", "that", "he", "was", "angry", "or", "agitated", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "I don't know about that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Did you actually see any of the shooting or did you just hear the shots go off?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "actually", "see", "any", "of", "the", "shooting", "or", "did", "you", "just", "hear", "the", "shots", "go", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "No, I've seen the shooting.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'ve", "seen", "the", "shooting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "So you saw this boy shooting your two friends?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "saw", "this", "boy", "shooting", "your", "two", "friends", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Obviously, very difficult to interview any young people in this kind of situation, but tell me, Monique, after you saw the shooting happen, who actually stopped this boy from shooting more of the students?", "question_tokens": ["Obviously", ",", "very", "difficult", "to", "interview", "any", "young", "people", "in", "this", "kind", "of", "situation", ",", "but", "tell", "me", ",", "Monique", ",", "after", "you", "saw", "the", "shooting", "happen", ",", "who", "actually", "stopped", "this", "boy", "from", "shooting", "more", "of", "the", "students", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "One of the staff running and told him to put that gun down, and he had his hands up in the air.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "of", "the", "staff", "running", "and", "told", "him", "to", "put", "that", "gun", "down", ",", "and", "he", "had", "his", "hands", "up", "in", "the", "air", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Monique"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Did you know anything about that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "anything", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Well, I do know he was being bullied.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "know", "he", "was", "being", "bullied", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "You said that he was being bullied?", "question_tokens": ["You", "said", "that", "he", "was", "being", "bullied", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nathaniel"]}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "CC", "RB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", ":", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "And once he'd been stopped from shooting anybody else, what then happened?", "question_tokens": ["And", "once", "he", "'d", "been", "stopped", "from", "shooting", "anybody", "else", ",", "what", "then", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "And after all that happened, they all sent the kids and the teachers were running to Nathaniel (ph) and then all the kids has -- were going to their classrooms.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "after", "all", "that", "happened", ",", "they", "all", "sent", "the", "kids", "and", "the", "teachers", "were", "running", "to", "Nathaniel", "(", "ph", ")", "and", "then", "all", "the", "kids", "has", "--", "were", "going", "to", "their", "classrooms", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "How long were you kept and locked down?", "question_tokens": ["How", "long", "were", "you", "kept", "and", "locked", "down", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Going to have to say for like two hours.", "answer_tokens": ["Going", "to", "have", "to", "say", "for", "like", "two", "hours", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Berendo"]}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "What do you feel about what happened to the school today?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "what", "happened", "to", "the", "school", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "I was like -- I was really scared of what happened, but I don't want to go to Berendo anymore because of what happened because I'm afraid it's going to happen again.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "like", "--", "I", "was", "really", "scared", "of", "what", "happened", ",", "but", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "go", "to", "Berendo", "anymore", "because", "of", "what", "happened", "because", "I", "'m", "afraid", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "happen", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["1:30 afternoon"]}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "CD", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "What do we know about the facts here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "we", "know", "about", "the", "facts", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Based on what we know is at approximately 1:30 afternoon, there's people watching the previews of a movie.", "answer_tokens": ["Based", "on", "what", "we", "know", "is", "at", "approximately", "1:30", "afternoon", ",", "there", "'s", "people", "watching", "the", "previews", "of", "a", "movie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Is that correct?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "correct", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "That's part of the investigation.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "part", "of", "the", "investigation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Can you confirm that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "confirm", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "You know, we can't -- you know, there's many things that are going out there, rumors, but I can tell you, he has been charged of second degree murder.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "we", "ca", "n't", "--", "you", "know", ",", "there", "'s", "many", "things", "that", "are", "going", "out", "there", ",", "rumors", ",", "but", "I", "can", "tell", "you", ",", "he", "has", "been", "charged", "of", "second", "degree", "murder", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "As a sheriff on the ground trying to deal with this gun violence epidemic, what do you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["As", "a", "sheriff", "on", "the", "ground", "trying", "to", "deal", "with", "this", "gun", "violence", "epidemic", ",", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "People commit violent crimes, you know, whether be a knife or a gun.", "answer_tokens": ["People", "commit", "violent", "crimes", ",", "you", "know", ",", "whether", "be", "a", "knife", "or", "a", "gun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "ORGAN: But you don't feel as a sheriff on the ground there should be any changes to the existing gun laws?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "But", "you", "do", "n't", "feel", "as", "a", "sheriff", "on", "the", "ground", "there", "should", "be", "any", "changes", "to", "the", "existing", "gun", "laws", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "No, as I go back to -- this is about, you know, we have mental health issues and substance abuse.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "as", "I", "go", "back", "to", "--", "this", "is", "about", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "have", "mental", "health", "issues", "and", "substance", "abuse", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "But, am I -- am I alone voice of insanity in this debate?", "question_tokens": ["But", ",", "am", "I", "--", "am", "I", "alone", "voice", "of", "insanity", "in", "this", "debate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "Lisa, tell me, really in simple short terms, what happened?", "question_tokens": ["Lisa", ",", "tell", "me", ",", "really", "in", "simple", "short", "terms", ",", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "We're on vacation.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "on", "vacation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "You don't quite sure how she died at the moment, is that the position?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "quite", "sure", "how", "she", "died", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "is", "that", "the", "position", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "No, they never gave me a diagnosis.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "they", "never", "gave", "me", "a", "diagnosis", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "EX", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "``", "DT", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", ",", "''", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "When did you realize, Lisa, that this was not your mother?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "realize", ",", "Lisa", ",", "that", "this", "was", "not", "your", "mother", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "I'm -- when I was approaching the casket before calling hours at the funeral home and I went up there and I looked at the hair and I looked at this woman's ears and I look at her nose and I said, \"No, this isn't mom, this isn't mom,\" and I got up and I walked out.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "--", "when", "I", "was", "approaching", "the", "casket", "before", "calling", "hours", "at", "the", "funeral", "home", "and", "I", "went", "up", "there", "and", "I", "looked", "at", "the", "hair", "and", "I", "looked", "at", "this", "woman", "'s", "ears", "and", "I", "look", "at", "her", "nose", "and", "I", "said", ",", "``", "No", ",", "this", "is", "n't", "mom", ",", "this", "is", "n't", "mom", ",", "''", "and", "I", "got", "up", "and", "I", "walked", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lisa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["St. Maarten"]}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "RP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "What happens next?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happens", "next", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "Well, we called right away down to the funeral home down to St. Maarten and said to the funeral director and that there was mix up, there was terrible mix up.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "called", "right", "away", "down", "to", "the", "funeral", "home", "down", "to", "St.", "Maarten", "and", "said", "to", "the", "funeral", "director", "and", "that", "there", "was", "mix", "up", ",", "there", "was", "terrible", "mix", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "Well that turned out to be a nonsense right?", "question_tokens": ["Well", "that", "turned", "out", "to", "be", "a", "nonsense", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "Right, right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", ",", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "make", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "ORTKKA: Terrible.", "answer_tokens": ["ORTKKA", ":", "Terrible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "But you don't know for sure, do you?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "do", "n't", "know", "for", "sure", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Is there any way that you can make any tests which could establish that it was you mother that was cremated?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "way", "that", "you", "can", "make", "any", "tests", "which", "could", "establish", "that", "it", "was", "you", "mother", "that", "was", "cremated", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Well supposedly they found some kind of bodily fluid in the casket.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "supposedly", "they", "found", "some", "kind", "of", "bodily", "fluid", "in", "the", "casket", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "What is your reaction to this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Well it's a horrific story and I'm so sorry to hear this tale.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "it", "'s", "a", "horrific", "story", "and", "I", "'m", "so", "sorry", "to", "hear", "this", "tale", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "Is there any likelihood of the ashes themselves revealing any DNA or indeed the fluid that was in the casket, is the second option more likely?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "likelihood", "of", "the", "ashes", "themselves", "revealing", "any", "DNA", "or", "indeed", "the", "fluid", "that", "was", "in", "the", "casket", ",", "is", "the", "second", "option", "more", "likely", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Yes that's a great question, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "that", "'s", "a", "great", "question", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "Do you have legal representation to take the appropriate action given that you've got to deal with St. Maarten and indeed with Canadian authorities?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "legal", "representation", "to", "take", "the", "appropriate", "action", "given", "that", "you", "'ve", "got", "to", "deal", "with", "St.", "Maarten", "and", "indeed", "with", "Canadian", "authorities", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "We haven't gotten any legal representation.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "n't", "gotten", "any", "legal", "representation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["St. Maarten"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Is the government helping you here, the US government?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "the", "government", "helping", "you", "here", ",", "the", "US", "government", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["US"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "CC", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "EX", "VBG", "RP", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "How would you like your wife Margaret to be remembered?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "like", "your", "wife", "Margaret", "to", "be", "remembered", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Oh, with love that she -- she is such a lovely woman and she -- it's so hard to explain it, but there was nothing that she could do to anybody that they wanted this or not or they needed something, she was always there, always there helping out, doing things for other people.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "with", "love", "that", "she", "--", "she", "is", "such", "a", "lovely", "woman", "and", "she", "--", "it", "'s", "so", "hard", "to", "explain", "it", ",", "but", "there", "was", "nothing", "that", "she", "could", "do", "to", "anybody", "that", "they", "wanted", "this", "or", "not", "or", "they", "needed", "something", ",", "she", "was", "always", "there", ",", "always", "there", "helping", "out", ",", "doing", "things", "for", "other", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Margaret"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Do you accept that if Chris Christie is being sincere and honest, and genuinely knew nothing about this Bridgegate affair that he has done all he could be possibly expected to do, since it all blew up?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "accept", "that", "if", "Chris", "Christie", "is", "being", "sincere", "and", "honest", ",", "and", "genuinely", "knew", "nothing", "about", "this", "Bridgegate", "affair", "that", "he", "has", "done", "all", "he", "could", "be", "possibly", "expected", "to", "do", ",", "since", "it", "all", "blew", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "JJS", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Well this is a self-inflicted wound Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "this", "is", "a", "self-inflicted", "wound", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Congressman Grimm, you support, I think, Chris Christie over this but it must have dented your faith in the way his run his administration, hasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Congressman", "Grimm", ",", "you", "support", ",", "I", "think", ",", "Chris", "Christie", "over", "this", "but", "it", "must", "have", "dented", "your", "faith", "in", "the", "way", "his", "run", "his", "administration", ",", "has", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Grimm", "Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "And I think that's what we all want to know right, Michael?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "what", "we", "all", "want", "to", "know", "right", ",", "Michael", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"], "LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Has he done all that he can do, do you think to deal with this crisis to date?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "done", "all", "that", "he", "can", "do", ",", "do", "you", "think", "to", "deal", "with", "this", "crisis", "to", "date", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "He stood before the national media for two hours, answered every question came before the legislator in the state in New Jersey today and was clear.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "stood", "before", "the", "national", "media", "for", "two", "hours", ",", "answered", "every", "question", "came", "before", "the", "legislator", "in", "the", "state", "in", "New", "Jersey", "today", "and", "was", "clear", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "What else do you want from this man?", "question_tokens": ["What", "else", "do", "you", "want", "from", "this", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Well, I suppose the obvious thing that struck me with all this and I'm always been a big fan of Chris Christie's, interviewed him several times and find him extremely impressive character in many ways.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "suppose", "the", "obvious", "thing", "that", "struck", "me", "with", "all", "this", "and", "I", "'m", "always", "been", "a", "big", "fan", "of", "Chris", "Christie", "'s", ",", "interviewed", "him", "several", "times", "and", "find", "him", "extremely", "impressive", "character", "in", "many", "ways", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Why do you think that is?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "that", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "Well were here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "were", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bieber"]}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "RB", "CC", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Is he just being a guy trying to release the shackles?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "just", "being", "a", "guy", "trying", "to", "release", "the", "shackles", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Listen, the business now, acts can happen quicker than ever and for, you know, for every Bieber, you know, along comes the Taylor Swift, or the lads in One Direction.", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "the", "business", "now", ",", "acts", "can", "happen", "quicker", "than", "ever", "and", "for", ",", "you", "know", ",", "for", "every", "Bieber", ",", "you", "know", ",", "along", "comes", "the", "Taylor", "Swift", ",", "or", "the", "lads", "in", "One", "Direction", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "You've been -- you've managed everyone from Fleetwood Mac, and the Eagles, Jackson 5, Prince, I mean all the naughty boys and those little (inaudible) I mean naughtiness and music go hand in hand, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "been", "--", "you", "'ve", "managed", "everyone", "from", "Fleetwood", "Mac", ",", "and", "the", "Eagles", ",", "Jackson", "5", ",", "Prince", ",", "I", "mean", "all", "the", "naughty", "boys", "and", "those", "little", "(", "inaudible", ")", "I", "mean", "naughtiness", "and", "music", "go", "hand", "in", "hand", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CD", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "CC", "DT", "RB", ":", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "You know, they handle it differently but, you know, I always tell them it's the music business.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "they", "handle", "it", "differently", "but", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "always", "tell", "them", "it", "'s", "the", "music", "business", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Fleetwood Mac"], "LOCATION": ["Eagles"], "PERSON": ["Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["LA Forum"]}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Why the LA Forum, why have you guys got together to do this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "the", "LA", "Forum", ",", "why", "have", "you", "guys", "got", "together", "to", "do", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Well, the LA Forum is really a unique, I wouldn't necessarily call it experiment but it's a one of a kind in the world venues.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "LA", "Forum", "is", "really", "a", "unique", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "necessarily", "call", "it", "experiment", "but", "it", "'s", "a", "one", "of", "a", "kind", "in", "the", "world", "venues", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jim"]}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "If you are a big music addict and you got Justin Timberlake in fact next week as well, what makes this special?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "are", "a", "big", "music", "addict", "and", "you", "got", "Justin", "Timberlake", "in", "fact", "next", "week", "as", "well", ",", "what", "makes", "this", "special", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Well, for one Jim and I share a common goal.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "for", "one", "Jim", "and", "I", "share", "a", "common", "goal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Justin Timberlake"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Who is the act you would most love to have been able to put on at this new forum?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "the", "act", "you", "would", "most", "love", "to", "have", "been", "able", "to", "put", "on", "at", "this", "new", "forum", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Unequivocally, the Beatles.", "answer_tokens": ["Unequivocally", ",", "the", "Beatles", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Right?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "You heard that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "heard", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "There's a big Beatles stand.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "big", "Beatles", "stand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "I presume you've invited lots in the places?", "question_tokens": ["I", "presume", "you", "'ve", "invited", "lots", "in", "the", "places", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]